Bruce Jackson and Diane Christian collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Subseries 4: Performers and writers
    - 332 / 1161 / Uncle Barry Satterfield and Nellie Satterfield / Marshall, AR / 19, June 27, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0814; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in.
      - 2. Pretty Sara
      - 3. Talk about ch[?]
      - 4. Rovin' Boys
      - 5. [?] Girl
      - 6. Rich Lady
    - 334 / 1163 / Ken Threadgill / Austin, Texas / 55 [?], July 9, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0816; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      This tape was recorded on a 1964 field trip. From the notes on the tape box back: Threadgill was born September 12, 1909; other biographical details are noted. Other information appears on a photocopy of the tape box interior.
      - 1. Land of My Boyhood Dream
      - 2. Mean Mama Blues
      - 3. Down in the Old Cherry Orchard
      - 4. Yodelling Ranger
      - 5. Desert Blues
      - 6. Waiting for a Train
    - 335 / 1164 / Son House / Tape 66, July 21, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0817; 1 sound tape reel: analog, four track, stereo; 7 in.
      Interview with Son House, at Phil Spiro's house, 31 Roberts Road, Cambridge. Johnny Price (of Peoria; stepbrother of Son House) plays and sings. Further biographical details about both men on the tape box.
    - 341A / 1170 / Mississippi John Hurt / #1, October 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0822; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, four track, stereo; 7 in.
      The manuscript log gives the date as November 25, 1964.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Talk
      - 2. Pay Day
        The tuning is an open E.
      - 3. Talk
      - 4. If You Don't Want Me You're Gonna Have to Have Me Anyhow
      - Side 2
      - 1. Hopjoint (standard)
        "First plays one finger, the way he heard, then his style (t, i, m)"
    - 342 / 1171 / Mississippi John Hurt / #2, October 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0823; 1 sound tape reel: analog, four track, stereo; 7 in.
      Recorded by Bruce Jackson and Ed Denson. See note for SR0822 regarding the date.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Talk on Stagolee
      - 2. Stagolee (song)
      - Side 2
      - 1. Welcome address
      - 2. Chicken
      - 3. Story of stinging snake
    - 343 / 1172 / Mississippi John Hurt / #3, October 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0824; 1 sound tape reel: analog, four track, stereo; 7 in.
      Only one side recorded. See note for SR0822 regarding the date.
      - 1. Talk on mojos
      - 2. When I Lay My Burden Down
      - 3. Royal Telephone
      - 4. Blue Harvest Blues - Shiverlie Red Blues
      - 5. Blind Man
      - 6. Shake That Thing
      - 7. Joe Turner
        The tape runs out.
    - 345 / 1173 / Mississippi John Hurt / #3 [?], October 27, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0825; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, mono; 7 in.
      Also present at the recording session: Ed Denson, Dave Evans, Skip James. Further details about the recording equipment set-up are noted on the tape box. According to the log, the date note on the tape box is in error (given there as October 26).
      - Side 1
      - 1. Grizzley Bear
      - 2. Avalon
      - 3. Richland Women
      - 4. Spike Driver
      - 5. Salty Dog
      - 6. Chicken
      - Side 2
      - 1. Candy Man
      - 2. Joe Turner
        Recorded in the key of B
      - 3. Creole Belle
      - 4. Toasts
      - 5. Louis Collins
      - 6. Cow Hooking [Cow Hooking Blues]
      - 7. Candy Man
    - 346 / 1174 / Mississippi John Hurt / Skip James / 2, October 27-28, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0826; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in.
      All cuts recorded on October 27, except the last three cuts on Side 2). Recorded at the same session as SR0825 (see notes for further details). A note next to I'm So Glad: "use 78 cut for connection."
      - Side 1
      - 1. Rubber Dolly - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 2. Devil - Skip James
      - 3. Cherry Ball [Cherry Ball Blues] - Skip James
      - 4. Talk on his first recording session - Skip James
      - 5. Cypress Grove [Cypress Grove Blues] - Skip James
      - 6. Talk
      - Side 2
      - 1. Hard Times [Hard Times Killing Floor Blues] - Skip James
      - 2. Sick Bed Blues - Skip James
      - 3. Illinois [Illinois Blues] - Skip James
      - 4. I'm So Glad - Skip James
      - 5. Omaha Blues - Skip James
      - 3. Illinois [Illinois Blues] - Skip James, October 28, 1964
      - 7. Washington Hospital (Washington D.C. Hospital Center Blues) - Skip James, October 28, 1964
      - 8. 4 O’clock Blues, October 28, 1964
    - 347 / 1175 / Mississippi John Hurt / Skip James, October 28, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0827; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono and stereo; 7 in.
      See note for SR0825; only Dave Evans was not present for this tape recording.
      - Side 1
      - 1. I'm Broke and Ain't Got a Dime - Skip James
      - 2. The Pal I Love - Skip James
      - 3. Around a Western Water Tank - Hurt and James [first time]
      - 4. Around a Western Water Tank - Hurt and James [second time]
      - 5. Rubber Dolly - Mississippi John Hurt
        Test
      - 6. The Brand New Old Time Spider Blues - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 7. Margie - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 8. Good Morning, Miss Carrie - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 9. Satisfied intro - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Side 2
      - 1. Satisfied - Mississippi John Hurt
        Picks up, misses a bit of the first stanza
      - 2. Red Wing - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 3. Keep Your Lamp Trimmed and Burning - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 4. Blind Man - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 5. Welcome table - Mississippi John Hurt
    - D-203 [DF 203] / Mississippi John Hurt, circa 1963-1966, AFC 2011/009: SR0828; 1 sound tape reel: analog, mono; 7 in.
      Mississippi John Hurt. The tape box has labels marked from Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University. Dub of tapes in the possession of Dick Waterman, Cambridge; a dub made sometime in 1964.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Do Lord
      - 2. When I Lay My Burden Down
      - 3. C.C. Rider
      - 4. Baby, That's All Right
        Al Wilson, harp
      - 5. Monday Morning Blues
      - 6. Creole Belle
      - Side 2
        Al Wilson plays harp on all songs on Side 2
      - 1. Avalon
      - 2. Can't Be Satisfied
      - 3. Spike Drivers Moan
      - 4. Cow Hooking
      - 5. Trouble I've Had It All My Days
      - 6. Sliding Delta
      - 7. Salty Dog
      - 8. Casey Jones
      - [songs listed on without a side designation]
      - 2. Nobody's Business
      - 3. Your Cruel Ways
      - 4. Loving Spoonful
      - 5. Candy Man
      - 6. Stackalee (runs out full on 2)
    - John Hammond / 1-4: WHRB bc (fr. studio tape) / 3-2: Vanguard VRS-9132 / 899, February 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0829; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      The song and credit list for Hammond's last record appears on the tape box back. The tape box has labels marked from Archives of Folk and Primitive Music, Indiana University.
      - 1-4 - John Hammond, live; tape for bc on WHRB recorded in Cambridge, Massachusetts on February 26, 1964
      - 3-2 John Hammond's last commercial record
    - Mike Seeger / Cornell Theater Concert / Set 1 / Reel 1 of 2, March 8, 1977, AFC 2011/009: SR0837; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Mike Seeger / Cornell Theater Concert / Set 1 / Reel 2 of 2, March 8, 1977, AFC 2011/009: SR0836; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - Mike Seeger in Concert / Cornell Theater / Set 2 / reel 1 of 1, March 8, 1977, AFC 2011/009: SR0833; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
    - 350 / Max Ochs and Al Wilson / [?] (drum [?]) / 1178, December 4, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0842; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Ragas (in 1964 Ochs was still part of The Seventh Sons, a raga fusion group; he was a founding member).
    - DF 205 [DF-208] / 912 / Bukka White, April 25, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0870; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Al Wilson, harp (blues harmonica). Recorded at Bates Hall (an auditorium), at the Boston YMCA. Dub copy from tape of Hal Edgar.
    - Son House (interview) [DF-209], November 4-5, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0871; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips, 1/4 track, mono; 7 in.
      November 4: interview by Dave Evans (Cambridge). November 5: interview by Al Wilson (Cambridge). Topics listed on the tape box (not specific to either interview): James McCoy (1926-30) -"Black Mama" and Preachin' Blues, Willie Wilson (1926-28), Reuben Lacy (1927), Paramount Recorder [?] (1930), "Dry Spell Blues" (hazy), Chronology 1926- (Lyon 1926-30, P[?] 1930 (4075 [?] [Lula 1930], Paramount Records: "Clarksdale Moan" and "Mississippi City F[?]," Charley Patton and Willie Brown (early 30s--"Shake It and Break It," "My Black Woman," "Depot Blues," "General MacAntony," "Pony Blues/Empire State Express," "Levee Camp Moan," "Barty Rooster"), Son House's musical theory - ma[?], AG + F(C), sharp and flat, dam [?], church songs, oral tradition and records, Patton and Brown's style compared, Son's career (alone 1928-30, Brown after 1930, [?] in 1934), (Lulu 1930, Robinsonville 1930-43, Rochester), his Blues Band, Joe Martin, Robert Johnson.
    - 408 / Skip James / 47 / I, September 14, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0872; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, two track, mono; 7 in.
      Skip James at Club 47, Cambridge. Tape 1 of 2
      - 1. Oh How I Love Jesus
      - 2. Crow Jane
      - 3. The Devil
      - 4. Hard Time Killin' Floor
      - 5. Catfish Blues
      - 6. Cherry Ball
        Beginning of set 2
    - 409 / Skip James / 47 / II, September 14, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0873; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, mono; 7 in.
      Skip James at Club 47, Cambridge. Tape 2 of 2
      - Side 1
      - 1. I'm So Glad
      - 2. Cypress Grove
      - 3. Special Rider
      - 4. Illinois
        Beginning of set 3.
      - 5. Bumblebee
      - 6. I'll Never Get Drunk No More
      - Side 2
      - 1. My Gal
      - 2. Last How Long Blues (piano)
      - 3. No More Hard Times (piano)
    - 348 / 1176 / Skip James / Mississippi John Hurt, October 30, 1964, November 1, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0874; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, mono; 7 in.
      First generation copy; the number in parentheses after each title refers to the original tapes. According to the manuscript log, Jackson made this copy for Ed Denson, for the master of the Piedmont LP of Skip. The original recordings were 1/2 track mono and stereo made on Fritz Fleron's Concertone, and dubbed to Jackson's Tandberg.
      - The Devil (19) - Skip James (vocal and guitar), November 1, 1964
        This song through "Worried Now" recorded on Track I. Recorded at the Unicorn (music venue).
      - Hard Time Killin' Floor (19) - Skip James (vocal and guitar), November 1, 1964
        Recorded at the Unicorn (music venue).
      - The Last How Long (9) - Skip James, October 30, 1964
        Recorded at Adams House music room, Harvard University.
      - Little Cow and Calf Gonna Die Blues (9) - Skip James, October 30, 1964
      - Four O’clock (9) - Skip James, October 30, 1964
      - 22-20 (9) - Skip James, October 30, 1964
      - Broke Ain't Got A Dime (17) - Skip James, November 1, 1964
      - Worried Now (17 or 19) - Skip James
      - Cypress Grove (?) - Skip James
        This song and those that follow are on Track IV.
      - John Henry (11) - Skip James, November 1, 1964
      - Stagolee (14) ([?] song) - Mississippi John Hurt, October 30, 1964
      - I'll Never Get Drunk No More (11) - Skip James, November 1, 1964
    - 913 / 160 / Bukka White / DF / 9B, April 24, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0875; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in.
      Bukka White with Al Wilson, harp. The list of titles here reflects the contents but may be presented out of actual order.
    - Side 1
      - I Don't Understand the Way You Do
      - Sic 'Em Dogs On Blues
      - Old Lady Blues
      - Discussion [spoken word]
      - Discussion (continued); breaks and picks up April 30, 1964
      - Discussion (conclusion)
      - Sleepy Man Blues
      - Parchman Farm Blues
      - Good Gin Blues
      - High Fever Blues
      - District Attorney Blues (part)
    - Side 2
      - District Attorney Blues
      - Fixin' to Die
      - Bukka's Jitterbug Swing
      - I Just Keeps On Wanting You (Herman E. Johnson)
      - Motherless Children (Herman E. Johnson)
      - Lumber Was a Flying (Emmanuel Dunn)
      - [Talk?] Sleepy Man Blues, Chicago 1940, Okeh, Washboard Sam
      - Strange Place Blues
    - 733 / Muddy Waters at Club 47 / March 2, 1966, March 1-3, 1966, AFC 2011/009: SR0876; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Recorded at Club 47, Cambridge.
      - Ch. 1 (Track 1) (March 2, 1966)
      - 1. Instrumental
      - 2. Instrumental
      - 3. Working on the High Line (MW)
      - 4. Baby, Please Don't Go (MW)
      - 5. She Moves Me (MW)
      - 6. Mean Mistreater (MW)
      - 7. (Introduction)
      - 8. 19 Years Old (MW)
      - 9. I Wanna Get Close to You, Baby (MW)
      - 10. Stormy Monday (MW-JC)
      - 11. She'll Be Comin' Round the Mountain (MW)
      - Track 2
      - 12. I Been Downhearted, Baby (JC)
      - 13. I'm Ready (instrumental) (JC)
      - 14. Meet Me In the Bottom (OS)
      - 15. (Ending) (OS)
      - 16. Five Long Years (MW)
      - 17. Walking Blues (MW) (March 3, 1966)
      - Ch. 2 (Track 3)
      - 18. Interview (MW) (March 1, 1966)
        Recorded by Carl F. Moxey
    - Dub of tapes from Tary Owens, Austin, circa 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0508; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, mono; 7 in.
      The name Mance Lipscomb appears on a tape box panel.
      - Side 1
      - Moore Brothers
    - 583 / Kevin Traynor / 5-14-69 / Tape #1, May 14, 1969, AFC 2011/009: SR0525; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Recorded in Buffalo, New York
      - 1. Sammy's Bar
      - 2. Traveling People
      - 3. Ould Triangle
      - 4. Verdant Braes of Screen
      - 5. The Spanish Lady
      - 6. Molly Malone
      - 7. The Nightingale (tape ran out)
    - 584 / Freddy King Band / 5-20-69 / Tape #1, May 20, 1969, AFC 2011/009: SR0526; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Side 1
      - 1. [unidentified] - James Peterson, guitar
      - 2. Don't Throw Your Love on Me So Strong - Jesse James, vocal
      - 3. [unidentified]
      - 4. Crosscut Saw (vocal - Jesse James)
      - 5. You Don't Have to Go - Jesse James, vocal
      - 6. [unidentified] - Jesse James, vocal
      - Side 2
      - 1. [unidentified] - Jesse James, vocal (continued)
      - 2. Dust My Broom
      - 3. [unidentified]
      - break (15 minutes)
      - 4. Interview with "Scotty," the booking agent
    - 585 / Freddy King Band / Tape #2, May 20, 1969, AFC 2011/009: SR0527; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      See note for SR0526
      - Side 1
      - 1. Papa's Got a Brand New Bag - Jesse James, vocal
      - 2. I've Been Loving You Too Long
      - 3. through 6. [unidentified]
        Freddy King, vocal on song #4.
      - 7. Get Out of My Life Woman
      - Side 2
      - 1. Play It Cool
      - 2. through 4. [unidentified]
      - break (20 minutes)
      - 5. [unidentified] - Jesse James, vocal
      - 6. You Can Make It If You Try
      - 7. Something You Got
    - 586 / Freddy King Band / Tape #3, May 20, 1969, AFC 2011/009: SR0528; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Reach Me, Baby - Jesse James, vocal
      - 2. [unidentified]
      - 3. Woke Up This Morning
      - 4. and 5. [unidentified]
      - 6. Blues Power
      - Side 2
      - 1. [unidentified]
      - 2. [unidentified] (vocal - Freddie King)
    - Glenn Ohrlin 1, AFC 2011/009: SR0675; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Cole Younger
      - 2. Stetson Hat
      - 3. Trail to Mexico
      - 4. Farruca
      - 5. Charlie Quantrell
      - 6. Nancy Till
      - 7. Hell-Bound train
      - Side 2
      - 1. High-Chin Bob
      - 2. Zebra Dan
      - 3. Bonny Black Bess
      - 4. Three Black Crows
      - 5. Bad News
        With spoken introduction
      - 6. Sporting Cowboy
      - 7. Cowman's Prayer
    - Glenn Ohrlin 2, AFC 2011/009: SR0674; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
    - 333 / 1162 / Glenn Ohrlin / Mountain View, Arkansas / 20, June 27, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0815; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      This tape was recorded on a 1964 field trip. "Castration of the Strawberry Roan"; recorded in Mountain View, Arkansas
    - 587 / Glenn Ohrlin / Friday night / Tape #1, December 20-21, 1968, December 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0529; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Glenn Ohrlin, fiddle; Kay Ohrlin, guitar. The first five songs on this tape were recorded on December 20, the balance of Side 1 and the first three songs of Side 2 were recorded on December 21, and the balance of the songs on Side 2 were recorded on December 24.
      - Side 1
      - 1. St. Paul's Waltz
      - 2. Bully of the Town
      - 3. Deep Ellen Blue
      - 4. Shadish (Norwegian)
      - 5. Put Your Little Foot
      - break (20 minutes) - Glenn, guitar
      - 6. Bunder Waltz
      - 7. Stoke Poker Waltz
      - 8. Glenn talking on phone
      - 9. White Cockaid [The White Cockade]
      - 10. Harding County Home
      - 11. Tiparary [Tipperary]
      - 12. Paddy Ryan
      - 13. Patty on the Turn Pike [Paddy on the Turnpike]
      - Side 2
      - 1. Strawberry Roan
      - 2. My Pretty Quadroon
      - 3. Young People Who Delight in Sin
      - Glenn's; Lon Finley (fiddle) and Glenn
      - 4. The Dago March
      - 5. Barb Wire
      - 6. Flop-Eared Mule
      - 7. Waltz of Vienna
      - 8. Redwing
      - 9. Turn Cinnamon Turn (Rock Her 'Til She Goes to Sleep)
      - 10. The Girl I Left Behind Me
      - 11. Billy in the Low Ground
      - 12. Peek-A-Boo Waltz
      - 13. Fallen Leaf
    - 588 / Glenn Ohrlin / 12-21-68 / Tape #2, December 21, 1968, December 23, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0530; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      From the tape box front: 12/23/68 / voneititers [?] / 1. Coon, Coon, Coon / Barbara Allen (from book Folk Songs of North America.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Battle of New Orleans (dulcimer)
      - 2. Fiddlers' Dance
      - 3. Bunker Hill
      - 4. Cripple Creek
      - 5. [unidentified]
      - 6. Norwegian Wood
      - break
      - 7. FFT [?] (autoharp)
      - 8. Flop Eared Mule
      - 9. [unidentified]
      - 10. Conversation
      - 11. Wednesday Night Waltz (Jodie singing)
      - 12. Good Old Country Days
      - 13. Boil Them Cabbage Down
      - 14. Baa Baa Black Sheep
      - 15. and 16. Judy and Sheryl - some songs
      - 17. and 18. Jodie and Sheryl - some songs
      - 19. Good Old Country Days (Jodie)
      - 20. Boil Them Cabbage Down (Jodie)
      - 21. Groundhog (Judy)
      - 22. Old Joe Clark
      - 23. Rank Stranger
      - break
      - 24. [unidentified] (tape ran out)
      - Side 2
      - 1. Willy Poor Boy (banjo and Sheryl [?])
      - 2. [unidentified]
      - 3. and 4. banjo [no other information]
      - break
      - 5. Bluebird (guitar)
      - 6. All the Good Times
      - 7. Freight Train
      - 8. Down in the Cane Break
      - break
      - 9. Rosewood Casket (autoharp)
    - 589 / Adrian Parks / 12-22-68 / Tape #3, December 22, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0531; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Side 1 - mandolin
      - 1. Rainbow (continued)
      - 2. Snow D[?]
      - 3. Silverbell
      - 4. Bully of the Town
      - 5. Red River Rag
      - 6. Rag Time Rag
      - 7. Give Me Oil in My Lamp (Betty Ann and Christine Parks)
      - 8. Goodnight Waltz
      - 9. Tennessee Wagoneer
      - 10. Over the Waves
      - 11. Soldiers Joy
      - 12. Nellytown [?] Waltz
      - Side 2 - fiddle, Alvin C.; guitar, Glenn
      - 1. (no name)
      - 2. [unidentified]
      - 3. Carol County Blues
      - 4. Peek-A-Boo
      - 5. and 6. [unidentified]
      - 7. Pretty Mollie
      - 8. Chicken Reel
    - 590 / Tape 4 / June 23, 1968, June 23, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0532; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Recorded by Glenn Ohrlin at Dick Smith's house in Buffalo, South Dakota
      - Side 1
      - 1. Don't Be Angry
      - 2. Moonlight and Skies
      - 3. Wabash Cannon Ball
      - 4. A True Blue Billy
      - 5. Cowboy Jack
      - 6. The Drunkard's Son
      - 7. Driftwood on the River
      - 8. Fortunes and Memories
      - 9. Pinto Carry Old Pike Pal [?]
      - 10. Bright's Waltz
      - 11. St. Paul Waltz
      - 12. Wabash Cannonball
      - 13. Sidewalks of New York
      - 14. Mountain Music
      - 15. Shaditch [?]
      - Side 2 - Meredith C[?]
      - 1. Sevenstep
      - 2. Rye Waltz
      - 3. Marching County
      - 4. The Parlor is a Pleasant Place
      - 5. Texas Cowhand
        From Pat Burt
      - 6. Blueside of Lonesome [Blue Side of Lonesome]
        From Jim Reeves
      - 7. Strawberry Roan
      - 8. Lane County Bachelor (Bud Hoag)
      - 9. San Antonio Ride/Sue City Sue [Sioux City Sue]/My Harding County Home - Dean Tarter
      - 10. Missouri Waltz - Dean Tarter and Glenn Ohrlin
      - 11. Tipperary
    - 591 / Tape 5, December 23-24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0533; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      The last song on Side 2 was recorded at Glenn's on December 24.
      - Judy - guitar ([?] singing) / Renee / Darlene (Tini)
      - Side 1
      - 1. Wildwood Flower
      - 2. Long Black Veil
      - 3. Hard Knocks
      - 4. I'll Fly Away (they would [?] back)
      - 5. [unidentified]
      - 6. Howdy Neighbors Howdy
      - 7. Knoxville Girl
      - 8. Green Grass
      - 9. Where Will I Shelter My Sheep
      - 10. Bud and Ishmael
      - 11. Walkin' Cane
      - Side 2
      - 1. Walkin' Cane (continued)
      - 2. Down in the Valley (from book Folk Songs of North America )
      - 3. Fallen Leaf (Kay singing)
    - 592 / Tape 6 / Glenn's house [Glenn Ohrlin], December 24, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0534; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in.
      - Side 1
      - Glenn's cowboy stories
      - Side 2
      - More of Glenn's stories
      - Conversation - any tunes from play-parties
      - The Sawmill Boy
    - 593 / Tape 7 / Ollie Gilbert, December 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0535; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - 1. Jimmy Randolph
      - 2. Rovin' Rambler
      - 3. Willow Green
      - 4. Lord Bateman
      - 5. I Am a Rambler and Gambler
      - 6. Precious Jewel
      - 7. Pretty Polly
      - 8. I'll Fly Away
      - 9. Home Alley [?] Home
      - 10. The Hypocrite Song
      - 11. The Circle Unbroken
      - 12. Floyd Collins
    - 594 / Tape 8 / Ollie Gilbert, December 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0536; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - 1. Rough and Rowdy Boys
      - 2. Utah/Cari [?]
      - 3. Three Little Babes
      - break (10 minutes)
      - 4. Picture on the War
      - 5. Martin, Mary, and Lazarus
      - 6. The Tramp in the Rain
      - 7. The Three Nights Drunk
      - 8. Let Him Go
      - 9. Butcher Boy
      - 10. Diver Boy
        Tape ran out; last verse missing
    - 595 / Tape 9 / Ollie Gilbert, December 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0537; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - 1. The Blind Child
      - 2. Orphan Girl
      - 3. Barbara Allen
      - 4. Civil War
      - 5. Uncle Rat
      - 6. Go Wash in the Beautiful Pool
      - 7. Angel Band
      - 8. [unidentified]
      - 9. The Old Churchyard
      - 10. Take a Vacation in Heaven
      - 11. Wayworn Traveler
      - 12. The Rich Lady
    - 596 / Tape 10 / Ollie Gilbert, December 26, 1968, AFC 2011/009: SR0538; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Joseph Looney
      - 2. The Golden Willow Tree
      - 3. Drummer Boy
      - 4. Story [1]
      - 5. Story [2]
      - 6. Cole Younger
      - 7. The Two Sisters
      - 8. Take This Hammer and Give It to the Captain
      - 9. "T" for Texas